[{"id": 1053, "question": "Mrs. Allen's husband died ten years ago when her son and daughter were still in high school. Mr. Allen had left some money, and since Mrs. Allen had managed a bookstore before she was married, she took the money and bought a shop in town. Later she moved the shop out to the shopping center. She was a pleasant woman; she worked hard and was well-informed about books, and so the bookstore prospered and she was able to hire a friend to help her. Laura Barnes, Mrs. Allen's friend and assistant, was also a widow. She had some free time and the need for a little extra-money, and so she took the job in the bookstore. She was too clever and friendly, and the two women were well-known in the neighbourhood as \"Mrs. A\"and \"Mrs. B\"....\n\nQ: How many people in all were there in the two women's families?   _  .", "options": ["At least 8", "At least 7", "At least 6", "At least 4"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3237, "question": "How can you build more word-of-mouth advertising ? In other words, why would your customers want to talk to their friends about their experience of doing business with you? When you perform your service or deliver your product competently , you are just doing what the customer expects. In order to increase the number of the customers who want to share their good experience with their friends, you must make your service impressive, going beyond what is expected. Recently my daughter Dawn and I had lunch with my team members at the Campbell House. The food and service were truly excellent. My daughter asked for her leftovers to be packed. They were returned to her in aluminum foil shaped like a swan . Guess what she talked about when she got home? How much more do you think it cost the Campb...\n\nQ: How did Dawn feel the moment she saw her packed leftovers?", "options": ["Disappointed and angry.", "Excited and crazy.", "Worried and unhappy.", "Surprised and pleased."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2128, "question": "The management and staff are happy to welcome you and will do all they can to make your stay an enjoyable one. We hope you will find the following suggestions and information of use to you. MEAL TIMES Our overnight charge includes a continental-type breakfast. Breakfast: 7:30-9:30 a. m. Lunch: 12:00-2:00 p. m. Afternoon tea: 4:00-5:30 p. m. Dinner: 7:00-9:15 p. m. Meals can be served in rooms at a small extra charge. We regret that owing to staff arrangements, meals cannot be served outside these times. In exceptional circumstances please consult one of our receptionists in advance. Light refreshments, including tea, coffee, biscuits and sandwiches, can be served in rooms between 10:00 a. m. and 11:00 p. m. except during the meal times listed above. Cold drinks are available in the room re...\n\nQ: If you do not wish to be disturbed, you should  _  .", "options": ["close the door all the time", "turn off all the light", "hang a sign on the door handle", "inform receptionist not to telephone you"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1241, "question": "When my friend went to Europe last summer, instead of snapping photographs of the Louvre or the Eiffel Tower or Stonehenge, she brought back 32 rolls of ... cathedral ceilings. Ceilings. For the 10 years I've known her I had never suspected that she was this passionate about stained glass. Still one of the best things about such pictures -- despite their obvious narrow appeal -- is that they can't help but tell us a great deal about the people who took them. So I shouldn't have been surprised when I got the roll of film back from my 5-year-old son's first camping trip. I opened the envelope, naively expecting to see pictures of the nightly campfire, the sun setting over the forest, and possibly even a deer or two. Instead, I saw an off-center picture of tennis shoes. Not even his tennis sh...\n\nQ: Which of the following proverbs best displays the author's final thought?", "options": ["Every dog will have its day.", "Every man has his hobby-horse.", "If a thing is worth doing, it's worth doing well.", "You can take a horse to the water but you cannot make him drink."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3142, "question": "From March 29 to April 19, a new version of Death of a Salesman was performedat tne Capital Theatre as the first in a series of foreign classics to mark the 60th anniversary of the Beijing People's Art Theatre.The last time this play was performed in Beijing was 29 years ago. Death of a Salesman was created in 1949 by Arthur Miller, who used it to reveal the weakness of the \"American Dream\" .The main character, Willy Loman, believes wholeheartedly in American capitalism, and desires to \"succeed\" but his own greed _ him in the end.Death of a Salesman's first performance was a huge hit on Broadway, where it shocked the American theatre world, and strengthened the 33-year-old Miller's status as a master of American theatre.The play won the Pulitzer Prize for Drama, New York Drama Critics' Cir...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage?", "options": ["The play received the Tony Award twice.", "Arthur Miller became famous in his forties.", "China didn't have \"salesman\" until the play was first performed here.", "The 1983 version of Death of a Salesman was directed by Ying Ruocheng."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 311, "question": "The computers and the Internet The computer is one of the most important inventions of today. Ever since it was invented, it has changed our lives a lot. People can do a lot of things with the computer. For example, some software can be used too help people finish their work. If one can't finish it at once, the computer can save it so that one can find it quickly the next time. When you talk about computer, you must mention the Internet.. The Internet is a huge worldwide collection of computer networks. A network is a small group of computers working together. You can find information about almost any topic in the world from this network.. For example, you can use the Internet instead of a library to find information about current issues for your homework. You can also find information abo...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is TRUE?", "options": ["One day the computer will completely replace humans.", "In modern times, the computer is the only most important invention.", "With the computer used in our daily lives, we can do some things easier than before.", "In the future, we can use the computer to do everything."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1219, "question": "The word I'm going to introduce to you today is-phubbing. Let's see the definition of this term:phubbing n. the act of snubbing someone in a social setting by looking at your cell phone instead of paying attention As you can probably guess, phubbing is a blend of phone and snubbing. The term was coined by a 23-year-old Melbourne resident Alex Haigh. Obviously, he got fed up with how people are always checking Facebook or Twitter on their phones when they are supposed to be interacting with someone face to face. He wanted to put an end to this social phenomenon, therefore he came up with this catchy term. And it did catch on. The word's earliest media mention dates back to June 2012, and in a little over a year's time, phubbing has already been picked up by almost all the mainstream media o...\n\nQ: What can we infer from this passage?", "options": ["People are easier to handle when seen on screen.", "Alex Haigh doesn't like the term \"phnubbing\"", "More and more people have become phubbers.", "We can phub if we have proper excuses."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 364, "question": "Throughout the world, clothing has many uses. It is used to provide protection from cold. It is also worn to prevent others from seeing specific parts of one's body. However, the parts of the body that must be covered vary widely throughout the world. Some clothing is worn to provide supernatural protection. Wearing a lucky shirt to take an exam is calling for supernatural assistance. People in all cultures use clothing and other forms of bodily decoration to communicate status , intentions and other messages. In North America, we dress differently for business and various leisure activities. North American women usually are much more knowledgeable of little difference in messages communicated by clothes than men. At times, this leads to silly mistakes of understanding of female intentions...\n\nQ: Some people wear lucky shirts to take an exam because they believe  _  .", "options": ["clothes can hide their fear for the exam", "clothes have extraordinary power", "shirts can make them more comfortable", "shirts provide protection against bad weather"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3083, "question": "Wild animals seem to have escaped the Indian Ocean tsunami , adding weight to ideas they possess a \"sixth sense\" for disasters, experts said on Thursday. Sri Lanka wildlife officials have said the giant waves that killed over 24,000 people along the Indian Ocean island's coast seemingly missed wild beasts, with no dead animals found. \"No elephants are dead, not even a dead hare or rabbit. I think animals can sense disaster. They have a sixth sense. They know when things are happening,\" H.D. Ratnayake, deputy director of Sri Lanka's Wildlife Department, said on Wednesday. The waves washed floodwaters up to 3 km (2 miles) inland at Yala National Park in the southeast, Sri Lanka's biggest wildlife reserve and home to hundreds of wild elephants. \"There has been a lot of evidence about dogs bar...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the text?", "options": ["It has been proved that animals have a \"sixth sense\".", "Research has been made on the special movements of animals before disasters.", "It's generally considered that animals can sense the coming of disasters.", "Animals have depended on the known senses to escape the Indian Ocean tsunami."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2335, "question": "How do you get a man to do his share of the house work? If you are like most of the women, you will face the question the hard way. A man will enjoy a clean, orderly house, but he usually won't make the effort to clean or organize it. This doesn't mean that a woman has to do all the housework; she may have to manage many of household duties, and request his partner's participation. A woman can often say that men and women should take equal responsibility for housework. Very few men are raised to be fully responsible for housework, and many men look on housework as women's work. On the other hand, most men will readily work around the yard, make repairs and complete projects on weekends or evenings, and it's important that you give your man appreciation for those things too. Most man will t...\n\nQ: According to the passage a man   _", "options": ["is willing to do housework.", "likes to be told how to do housework", "is taught to be responsible for housework from childhood", "likes a clean house but doesn't make effort to do it."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 977, "question": "Schouten University is a highly respected online education provider offering officially-recognized degree programs across the globe. Our mission is to provide students with a high-quality mixed learning MBA program and personal coaching to help them to become world-class managers. MBA with Unique Skills & Personal Development Program Students will benefit from 30 years of soft skills training experience from Schouten & Nielsen, the leading soft skills training institute in Europe. To become an effective manager, theory alone is not enough, and being able to put theory into practice is more important today than ever before. With the Schouten University MBA program you will have the unique opportunity to develop such soft skills as influencing skills, leadership skills, communication skills ...\n\nQ: The time to participate the residential weeks is   _  .", "options": ["flexible", "fixed", "unnecessary", "inconvenient"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1180, "question": "Nowadays everybody seems to think that they know English. Many people speak it but few speak it really well. Practice is necessary in speaking English well. Reading is also one of the things that will help you to speak English better. Read whenever you can and whatever you like! Read papers and Internet sites that you like in English every day. Then, you will see that the number of known words is increasing and you are able to speak with more skills. Then you will have made the foundations and a good basis of English. It is not good to stop and get stuck there. Going to England or an English speaking country is a good choice, but many people cannot afford it. If you cannot go, reading and speaking with your friends will also help you to practice your English. However, I think that it is ve...\n\nQ: Which of the following could be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["How to Improve Your Language Skills", "How to Speak English Well", "Speaking English", "Practice, Practice"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2798, "question": "There are many acceptable varieties of English throughout the world. Whichever variety is used in your country, the most important thing is that students' pronunciation must be good enough for another person to understand what they are trying to say. In a PPP lesson, teachers naturally include a good model of the pronunciation when they are presenting new vocabulary, grammar or functional language. It is important to start by helping your students recognize sounds before you expect them to produce them. Spoken British English has 44 sounds, but there are only 26 letters in the alphabet for written English. This sometimes makes English pronunciation and spelling different, so it is not always best to write words on the blackboard at the early stages. Also, some sounds in English do not exis...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Suggestions on Teaching English Pronunciation.", "Listening Comes First in Teaching Pronunciation.", "The English Phonetic Alphabet and Pronunciation.", "Other Things to Be Done besides Pronouncing Every Word."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3128, "question": "In the last 500 years nothing about people--not their clothes, ideas, or languages has changed as much as what they eat. Chocolate drink was first made from the seeds of the cacao tree by South American Indians. The Spanish introduced it to the rest of the world during the 1500s. And although it was very expensive, it quickly became popular, In London, shops where chocolate drinks were served became important places. Some still exist today. The potato is also from the New World. Around 1600, the Spanish brought it from Peru to Europe, where it soon was widely grown. Ireland became so dependent on it that thousands of Irish people starved when the crop failed during the years of 1845--1846, and thousands more were forced to go to live in America. There are many other foods that have travele...\n\nQ: From the passage we can conclude   that millions of people drink coffee   _  .", "options": ["in the morning", "at noon", "in the afternoon", "in the evening"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1123, "question": "Last week, I bought an alarm system for about $ 450. It consisted of a control unit with three other small units. I put the control unit in the sitting room and fastened the other units by the front door, back door and living-room windows. The instructions told us to choose three numbers, so we chose 491, the last three numbers of our telephone number. Now I must explain how the alarm works: 1. There is a power siren in the control unit. It makes a very loud noise. 2. Each of the small units sends out beams or rays in different directions. If anything moves, it breaks a beam. This sends a signal to the control unit. The siren makes a noise that you can hear 50 meters away. 3. When we go to bed, I press the three buttons numbered 4, 9 and 1. Then we have 30 seconds to get out of the room be...\n\nQ: The purpose of the writer in writing the passage is to  _  .", "options": ["tell us that the alarm system doesn't work", "tell us an interesting experience", "show us how the alarm system works", "make it clear that he wants to give away his alarm system"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1393, "question": "Lonely Planet Publications is the largest guidebook publisher in the world. With over 650 titles sold in 118 countries, it annually sells six million copies, giving guidance to travelers in locations worldwide. Tony Wheeler and his wife Maureen Wheeler were the founders of Lonely Planet Publications and its first writers. They put together Lonely Planet's first publication- Across Asia on the Cheap. Originally from Australia, the couple had decided to travel from Europe back home to Australia overland-going through the countries of Iran, Afghanistan, Pakistan, India, Nepal, and South-East Asia, to eventually reach Australia. Tourist facilitres were limited in these countries, so if travelers wanted to go there, they had to eat and sleep locally. Many of these travelers were young and adven...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["How the Lonely Planet Publications developed.", "How to have a trip in an economical way.", "The Wheelers liked traveling around the world.", "The Wheelers wrote two books about traveling."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1628, "question": "Nick Vujicic was born with no arms or legs, but he doesn't let this stop him. The brave 26-year-old man plays football and golf, and swims, in spite of the fact that he has no arms or legs. Nick has a small foot on his left side, which helps him balance and makes him able to kick. He uses his one foot to type, write with a pen and pick things up. \"I call it my chicken drumstick ,\" joked Nick, who was born in Melbourne, Australia, but now lives in Los Angeles. \"I'd be lost without it. When I get in the water I float because 80 percent of my body is lungs and my drumstick acts as a propeller .\" \"He's very modest, but he gets marriage proposals from women all the time,\" said Nick's friend Steve Appel. \"He would love to get married and start a family, but he's waiting for the right girl to com...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE?", "options": ["Nick's parents couldn't afford the hospital bill.", "Nick is living in Melbourne, Australia now.", "Nick's father was to blame for his disability.", "Nick learned to be independent at a young age."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 422, "question": "Do you love holidays but hate gaining weight? You are not alone. Holidays are times for celebrating. Many people are worried about their weight. With proper planning, though, it is possible to keep normal weight during the holidays. The idea is to enjoy the holidays but not to eat too much. You don't have to turn away from the foods that you enjoy. Here are some tips for preventing weight gain and maintaining physical fitness: Don't skip meals. Before you leave home, have a small, low-fat meal or snack . This may help to avoid getting too excited before delicious foods. Control the amount of food. Use a small plate that may encourage you to \"load up \". You should be most comfortable eating an amount of food about the size of your fist . Begin with soup and fruit or vegetables. Fill up befo...\n\nQ: Which of the following can NOT help people to lose weight according to the passage?", "options": ["Eating lean meat.", "Creamy food.", "Eating raw fruit or vegetables.", "Physical exercise."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2269, "question": "The students in America usually begin high school at the age of 13 or 14. Some leave at the age of 16. But most finish the 4-year high school study. They do not get their first full-time work or begin college studies until they are 17 or 18 years old. The high school day is about 7 hours long. Part of the day is made into classes of about 50 minutes long. The students have lunch in the middle of the day. American students study English, history, math, science, art and languages. Some also learn job skills. They can learn how to use a computer or how to mend a car. Other students may learn by working in an office, a hospital or other places one day a week. Jean Wilton Anderson is 16 years old. She lives with her parents and two younger brothers in Bethesda, Maryland, near Washington D.C. Je...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not true to the high school?", "options": ["The school day usually lasts for 7 hours.", "The students only have 6 subjects to learn.", "Each class will last for 50 minutes.", "The students can learn some skills out of the school."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 808, "question": "If you like bicycling as much as you like playing ball and can't seem to decide between the two sports, you may want to consider cycle ball--a fun sport that adopts the key attributes from both activities and transforms it into a totally new game.. Also known as red ball, the game was invented in 1893 by German laborers who wished to play polo , but could not afford horses. While the sport has not _ in North America, it is very fashionable in Europe and even Japan. Played in an indoor court, cycle ball is similar to soccer in many ways--the aim is to score as many goals as possible, and only the goalkeeper is allowed to touch the ball. The one big difference? Use of legs is forbidden. Instead, players have to guide the ball across the court, using the front wheels of their bicycles or with...\n\nQ: What does the passage mainly talk about?", "options": ["The origin and development of soccer", "The differences between cycle ball and soccer.", "The most popular sports game in the world.", "A new and fun sports game--cycle ball"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2093, "question": "When George was thirty-five, he bought a small plane and learned to fly it. He soon became very good and made his plane do all kinds of tricks . George had a friend, whose name was Mark. One day George offered to take Mark up in his plane. Mark thought, \" I've traveled in a big plane several times, but I've never been in a small one, so I'll go. \" They went up, and George flew around for half an hour and did all kinds of tricks in the air. When they came down again, Mark was glad to be back safely, and he said to his friend in a shaking voice, \"Well , George, thank you very much for those two trips in your plane.\" George was very surprised and said, \" Two trips? \" \" Yes, my first and my last. \" answered Mark....\n\nQ: When George did some tricks with his small plane, Mark was   _  .", "options": ["unhappy", "excited", "frightened", "surprised"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3063, "question": "A single letter written by Albert Einstein was sold for more than $400, 000. But could an e-mail printout or an electronic file reach similar heights? That's the question facing those who deal in the literary artifacts of public figures, as they struggle to work out how to do business in the electronic world where information can be copied and spread out more easily than ever before. \"Booksellers, collectors and libraries are already trading in digital objects,\" Joan Winterkorn, a researcher told people. When Emory University Library bought author Slaman Rushdie's archives in 2006, it received a desktop computer, three laptops, a hard drive and a smart phone along with his paper flies. And the writer John Updike, who died last month, started using computers in the 1980s, Winterkorn pointed...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of the example mentioned in Para. 1?", "options": ["To introduce the topic of the passage.", "To show that some written letter are of great value.", "To get readers interested in electronic documents.", "To tell us to pay attention to public figures, artifacts."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2556, "question": "Bernie was smart and wanted to be his own boss.When Bernie was 25 he took a wife. Bernie had saved some money and decided on a dry goods and grocery store combined. Marie had a knack for arranging the merchandise to appeal to customers and Bernie didn't mind the long hours. He was happy, and life was good.The business thrived until the great depression hit the entire country. No one had money to purchase pretty things or even food. In 1930, Marie had a heart attack and left Bernie alone. Following Marie's death, which Bernie felt was brought about from worrying about the store, He lost interest in everything. He had few customers and did not make them feel welcome, Bernie wandered about the store , dusting a bit and sweeping the floor. His inventory remained almost the same, as nothing muc...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that sales at the store has been   _   throughout the 1930s.", "options": ["decreasing", "increasing", "changing", "reducing"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1165, "question": "What's A Real Friend? You can have the same neighbors for years. You love them or you think you love them. And you hope that they love you. But do you ever really understand them? Charlie Kemp and his family lived next door to me for 15 years. We were good friends all the time. I enjoy friendship. I think it's the best thing in the world. And friendship with the Kemps was easy because they seemed to welcome it. They were interesting and clever people. Their house caught fire twice, and twice the whole family slept in mine. They are always losing things like money, keys and watches. Pictures fell off the walls, the children fell out of bed ... I was their neighbor and their friend. Life was always interesting, never dull. Best of all, I liked the whole family. One day, I lit a fire in the g...\n\nQ: The author's experience tells us that   _  .", "options": ["a friend in need is a friend indeed", "it is difficult to understand a person, even your friend", "anyone is sure to be friendly to you if you are friendly to him", "friendship is the best thing in the world"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1764, "question": "Up, Up, and Away! An adventurer who became the first person to fly across the English Channel on a cluster of balloons has launched a house into the sky just like in the hit movie Up-in reparation for a more ambitious journey and a new record Fearless Trappe , from North Carolina, stepped into the cartoon themed home before flying above the leon International Balloon Festivel in Mexico more than a week ago. The 38-year-old Trappe was using the event as a warm-up for his planned trans-Atlantic flight scheduled for next summer ,He aims to complete the 2,500-mile journey in a seven-foot lifeboat carried by 365 huge helium ballooms The brave man is learning to sail a lifeboat ,in case he meeds to ditch into the ocean during the danger-filled adventure He sill fly at between 18,000 feet and 25,...\n\nQ: About the ambitious journey ,which is NIT mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["When he will fly", "How high he sill fly", "How far he will fly", "How long it will take him"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 634, "question": "When people who are nature lovers worldwide wish all humans to realize the importance of their natural surroundings, many Australians are turning caring for the environment into a way of life. Julie, an Australian housewife in Brisbane is one such example. Even though autumn is approaching Australia's Brisbane in April, one can still watch colorful blooming flowers in Julie's little garden, as she tells that in her community,\"Each of us has a beautiful yard. The whole community, from children to elderly people, takes care of the environment as if they are taking care of their own garden.\" \"Gardening is the most popular club in our community,\" she says. \"A lot of retired people don't just regularly organize gardening lectures, but also personally visit families in the community to provide g...\n\nQ: What do we know about Julie from the passage?", "options": ["She finds it embarrassing to walk on the grass.", "She once stepped on a dog's waste.", "She is quite in favor of raising a dog.", "She takes pride in her community."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1153, "question": "Some nations think they must have more and more babies, more and more people, if they are to remain strong and free. Actually, this is not so. Very often in history, small nations have conquered large ones. It's not so much the size of the army as its organization and the technical level of its weapons. Thus, Greece took over Persia in the 300s B.C., Great Britain took over India in the 1700s, even though Persia and India had far bigger population than Greece and Great Britain. If a nation wishes to avoid being dominated by its neighbors, its best chance is to raise its standard of living and its level of technology. _ can be done best by not allowing its population to grow to such a point that it is sunk in misery and poverty. In fact, the worst way in which a nation can try to avoid bein...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that if a country had fewer people,   _  .", "options": ["it could still remain strong", "it would be defeated by a strong neighbour", "its standard of living could be high", "its people would live misery"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2240, "question": "Supermarket Morrisons today announced to launch an online shopping operation within two years in a move to catch up with its web-savvy rivals. The UK's fourth biggest supermarket said Morrisons.com would offer grocery and non-food products but would take time to build from zero. As part of its online development, Morrisons - the only one of the \"Big Four\" grocers to have a significant internet business - revealed it had invested PS32 million in a 10% stake of a New York-based online grocer. The announcement came as Morrisons posted a 13% increase in underlying pre-tax profits of PS869 million in the year to January 30. Morrisons is implementing a growth strategy which is focused on expanding its e-commerce business and moving into the convenience store market. It has earmarked PS3 billion ...\n\nQ: FreshDirect severs 600,000 customers in    _    .", "options": ["Connecticut", "New Jersey", "New York", "certain states"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3355, "question": "Iceland, an island just south of the Arctic Circle, has fairly mild winters, thanks to warm ocean currents. Time your vacation here during the winter months to take advantage of off-season deals. Off-season means good deals on flights, hotels and tours. You may also find that the locals are a bit friendlier and more welcoming when tourists aren't arriving in crowds. In the winter months, there are less than seven hours of daylight; thus, chances are good you'll catch sight of the northern lights. Sunsets are also beautiful at this time, making for some great photo opportunities. In Iceland, winter is the perfect time to hike glaciers, go ice climbing, explore caves made out of hardened lava and much more. One of the most popular activities is off-roading in a specially-equipped \"super jeep...\n\nQ: According to the article, how do visitors to Iceland have fun in the winter?", "options": ["They learn how to ski down the mountains.", "They photograph famous historic sites..", "They explore the countryside in well made vehicles..", "They spend a week at one of the seaside resorts."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 642, "question": "The Healthy Habits Survey shows that only about one third of American seniors have correct habits.Here are some findings and expert advice. 1.How many times did you brush your teeth yesterday? *Finding:A full 33% of seniors brush their teeth only once a day. *Step:Remove the 300 types of bacteria in your mouth each morning with a batteryoperated toothbrush.Brush gently for 2 minutes,at least twice a day. 2.How many times did you wash your hands or bathe yesterday? *Finding:Seniors,on average,bathe fewer than 3 days a week.And nearly 30%wash their hands only 4 times a day-half of the number doctors recommend. *Step:We touch our faces around 3,000 times a day-often inviting germs to enter our mouth,nose,and eyes.Use toilet paper to avoid touching the door handle.And,most important,wash your ...\n\nQ: The text probably comes from   _  .", "options": ["a guide book", "a popular magazine", "a book review", "an official document"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 376, "question": "My friend Mike was shaking his head in disbelief. \"That young woman who just waited on me,\" he said, pointing to an employee of the fast food restaurant where we were eating, \"had to call someone over to help her count change. The cash register showed her I needed 99 cents, but she couldn't figure out how to count out the coins.\" I understood Mike's concern. What we have done is to create several generations of individuals most of whom have no idea how to reason; how to do simple math; how to do research; or, finally, how to be creative . The reason for this is our overuse of information technology: video games, television, digital watches, calculators, and computers. Information technology feeds us information without requiring us to think about it and let us perform operations without un...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that the author believes   _  .", "options": ["calculators help children expand their imagination", "reading benefits children more than electronics do", "there's no place for electronics in the classroom", "information technology does us a lot of good"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2219, "question": "Davey wanted to play baseball. But fifty years ago, in his small town, he couldn't find enough players for two full teams or an empty lot big enough for a field. And when he played ball in his back yard, he just broke windows and got into trouble. So Davey began playing with a plastic golf ball and a broom handle for a bat. When his dad, David Mullaney, a former semi-pro baseball pitcher , realized his son was hurting his arm trying to throw curves with the little plastic ball, he decided to find a better solution. Mullaney got a bunch of hollow plastic _ from a local factory, sat down at his kitchen table and began cutting different size holes in the balls with a razor knife. He thought maybe the holes would alter the ball's flight and help his son throw curves and sliders without hurting...\n\nQ: The two important factors for Mullaney's successful family business are  _  .", "options": ["time and fortune", "persistence and creativity", "quality and fame", "cooperation and efforts"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 667, "question": "A treasure trove hidden for centuries has been discovered in the underground vaults of a temple in southern India. The treasures include gold, diamonds and precious stones. The estimated value of the hoard is reportedly 22 billion US dollars. Hundreds of armed police have been deployed around the temple. Meanwhile, a debate about how to use the money has also broken out across the country. After discovering the treasure trove in Sri Padmanabhaswamy Temple in the southern Indian state of Kerala, the local government has assured security of the temple. Elaborating on the security arrangements, Venugopalan Nair, Additional Director General of the Kerala Police, says the latest security devices are being used to guard the temple. Venugopalan Nair, Additional Dir. Gen. of Kerala Police, said, \"...\n\nQ: What G.Jayasekharan Nair said means that  _", "options": ["what the government does means little", "the crowd will make trouble without proper control", "more effective measures should be taken", "the temple is of great value"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1072, "question": "Best places to visit in Australia Are you looking for the best places to see in Australia? Here are the top 5 places to visit in Australia. It includes the best, the most beautiful and the most famous. Sydney For those who have made a flight from the other side of the world, if you come and don't see Sydney, it is a bit like going to Germany and not drinking a beer, or to England and not seeing London, or America and not trying a hot dog. There is plenty to see and do in Sydney apart from the well known attractions of the Harbour Bridge, the Opera House, and Bondi beaches. Byron Bay Located in New South Wales, just south of the Queensland border, Byron Bay is popular with not just international tourists, but is also a favorite holiday destination of Australians. The lighthouse is amazing a...\n\nQ: Where can you see unique and endangered animals in Australia?", "options": ["Daintree Rainforest", "The Great Barrier Reef", "Byron Bay", "Sydney"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1294, "question": "In many countries today, laws protect wildlife. In India the need for such protection was realized centuries ago. About 300 B.C. an Indian writer described forests that were somewhat like national parks today. The killing of game animals was carefully governed. Some animals were fully protected. Within the forest, nobody was allowed to cut trees, burn wood, or trap animals for their furs. Animals that became dangerous to human visitors were trapped or killed outside the park, so that other animals would not become uneasy. The need for wildlife protection is greater now than ever before. About a thousand sorts of animals are in danger of extinction, and the speed at which they are being destroyed has been putting on. With mammals, for example, the speed of extinction is now about one sort e...\n\nQ: According to the report, men trying to save wildlife are thinking about  _  as well.", "options": ["the animals in national parks", "stricter laws against hunting", "the trees in the forests", "the needs of people"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3478, "question": "Once upon a time, on an isolated island in the Java sea, lived short people who dominated(, ) the food chain. Standing no more than three and a half feet tall, these human ancestors hunted giant rats, lumbering lizards , and _ elephants. It sounds a bit like a fairy tale, but it's true. Unearthed relics on the island uncovered the remains of a race of tiny human ancestors. Homo floresiensis, as the newly discovered species has been named, apparently could date back to 13,000 years ago. This means they have a lot in common with modern humans. So how and why did these people get so small? Scientists suspect that it's due to the fact that this race lived on an isolated island with limited resources. Take the miniature elephants for example. When elephants first came to the island either by sw...\n\nQ: What might be the most suitable title of the passage?", "options": ["The history of short people", "Short people from a fairy tale", "The proofs on short people", "Short people on an isolated island"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 400, "question": "The Internet has led to a huge increase in credit-card fraud. Your card information could even be for sale in an illegal web site. Web sites offering cheap goods and services should be regarded with care. On-line shoppers who enter their credit-card information may never receive the goods they thought they bought. The thieves then go shopping with your card number -- or sell the information over the Internet. Computers hackers have broken down security systems, raising questions about the safety of cardholder information. Several months ago, 25, 000 customers of CD Universe, an on-line music retailer , were not lucky. Their names, addresses and credit-card numbers were posted on a Web site after the retailer refused to pay US $157, 828 to get back the information. Credit-card firms are now...\n\nQ: You are shopping on the site: http: // www. Shopping. com, and you want to buy a TV set, what does this article suggest to do?", "options": ["Order the TV set at once.", "Do not buy the TV set on this site.", "E-mail the site your credit-card information.", "Tell the site your password and buy the TV set for you."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 240, "question": "Discover Artistic Talents across the Country Redtory, Guangzhou Redtory, established in 2009, is a spacious art district often referred to as Guangzhou's 798. Made up of more than 30 old halls, mostly buildings of red brick, the place was originally built in 1956 as Chinese largest can factory. Some of the rusty machines from the old factory have been kept as art equipment, giving the zone an old charm. Where: No. 128 Yuancun Siheng Road, Tianhe District, Guangzhou Opening hours: Mon-Sun 10:30 am-9 pm Tank Loft, Chongqing This 12,000-square-meter art center was established on the site of a used military tank warehouse . It is the largest contemporary art base in western China, featuring modern exhibition, galleries, design studios and art bookstores. The art zone is located on the campus o...\n\nQ: Tank Loft, Chongqing is quite different from the others in  _  .", "options": ["size", "site", "feature", "weather"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 295, "question": "Children today would rather toy with new technologies. The role of children has changed as well as that of teens. The world has truly evolved throughout the years. Today,a typical day in the life of a five year old is entirely different from what it once was. A few decades ago children used to work. They did the kind of work parents do today. Today there are shows on which children are putting pounds of makeup on and have flashing things all over their bodies. This makes a child want to _ all of their imperfections. They think they have to look perfect all the time. Teens have changed as well. My grandma got married when she was thirteen. Girls who had an arranged marriage had no time to play because they were expected to cook, clean,take care of the kids, and do housework every single day...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that nowadays teenagers   _  .", "options": ["do housework as their parents did", "are having a social life in richer ways", "are seldom satisfied with what they have", "don't appreciate and value life"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1370, "question": "\"Make-A-Wish\" is one of the world's most well-known charities . It makes wishes come true for childrenwho have serious illnesses. It gives them hope and joy and helps them forget about their health problems and have fun. It all started in 1980 in Phoenix, Arizona. Christopher was a 7-year-old boy who was very sick. He always dreamed ofbecoming a police officer. Tommy Austin and Ron Cox, two police officers, made his wish come true. They gaveChristopher a tour of the city in a police helicopter and made a real police uniform for him. There are four kinds of wishes children usually have: I wish to go. Children usually want to travel or go to a concert, a game or a park. I wish to meet. Children sometimes want to meet their favourite actors, singers or players. I wish to be. Some children wis...\n\nQ: What did the two police officers do for Christopher?", "options": ["They gave him a computer.", "They gave him a tour of the city.", "They took him to a concert.", "They took him to the hospital."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1517, "question": "Women had a significant part to play during World War II,which was the time when women also made their own contributions.Some women's great efforts and their names have been recorded in history.Here's a look at some of the strong figures of women in World War II. Tatiana Nikolaevna Baramzina was born in Glazov of Russia on December 12,1919.In 1943,she was sent to the Central Women's Sniper Training School and upon her graduation in April,she was further sent to the front.She managed to kill around 16 enemies in the first three months!Unfortunately,she was captured by the enemies and was killed on the fifth of July in 1944.Today,the street where she grew up has been renamed in her memory. Anne Frank was a Germanborn Jewish girl who was wellknown for the publication of her diary that describ...\n\nQ: Which of the four women heroes died the youngest?", "options": ["Tatiana Baramzina.", "Anne Frank.", "Margaret Ringenberg.", "Hannah Szenes."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2784, "question": "There are two factors which determine an individual's intelligence. The first is the sort of brain he is born with. Human brains differ considerably, some being more capable than others. But no matter how good a brain he has to begin with, an individual will have a low order of intelligence unless he has opportunities to learn. So the second factor is what happens to the individual--the sort of environment in which he is reared . If an individual is handicapped environmentally, it is likely that his brain will fail to develop and he will never attain the level of intelligence of which he is capable. The importance of environment in determining an individual's intelligence can be demonstrated by the case history of the identical twins, Peter and Mark X. Being identical, the twins had identi...\n\nQ: This passage can be best titled  _  .", "options": ["Intelligence and Environment", "Measuring Your Intelligence", "The Case of Peter and Mark", "How the brain Influences Intelligence"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3140, "question": "Harry potter and The Hunger Games haven't been big hits for nothing. Lots of teens still read quite a lot. But a study shows a clear decrease over time. Nearly half of 17-year-olds say they read for pleasure no more than one or two times a year. That's way down from ten years ago. The digital revolution means there are more platforms than ever to read on. Jim Steyer has been studying the effect of technology on children. He has four kids and has seen the trend most with his 16-year-old. \"I start to see it in our 10-year-old as well, because he is reading less and less, and more and more attracted to some of the digital media platforms that he has access to, and that he didn't have access to when he was 6 or 7 years old,\" he says. The studies don't say that kids are reading less because the...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the text?", "options": ["What books do teens like to read the most?", "Why aren't teens reading like they used to?", "How can teens read on electronic platforms?", "When will teens turn to books for fun again?"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1634, "question": "One day a student went to see his teacher. He had been given an important position and now was coming to say goodbye to his teacher. The old man asked him how he would live among high officials. The student answered, \" I will be all right. I have prepared a hundred high hats, one for each official I will meet. I am sure I will succeed.\" The teacher got angry on hearing this. \"What?\" he cried. \"Is this what ten years of my teaching has made of you? Nothing but flatterer ?\" \"Excuse me, honored master,\" the student rose to his feet and apologized hurriedly. \"But you have always been absorbed in your studies and don't know how vulgar the world has come to be. There are few men in the world who are above flatterers like you.\" \"There is something true in what you said,\" the teacher nodded, smili...\n\nQ: The student came to say goodbye to his teacher because  _  .", "options": ["he had got hundred hats to sell", "he had got a fairly high position in society", "he wanted to see his parents in his home town", "he moved away to another city"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2163, "question": "*1. Malan Flower: China Children's Art Theatre stages a fairy tale musical \"Malan Flower\" this weekend. Beautiful Malan flowers were blossoming everywhere on Malan Mountain, and hard-working girl Xiao Lan was married to the god of flowers, Ma Lang. They lived a happy life in harmony with Grandpa Tree. and all the lovely little animals. However, greedy Old Cat made use of the jealousy of elder sister Da Lan to kill Xiao Lan, in an attempt to keep the magic Malan flower under her possession. This fairy tale entertained three generations of Chinese youth. Time: 7: 30 p. m., until August 21 Place: The Great Theatre of the Cultural Palace of the Nationalities, west of Xidan Area Tel: 6602-2530 *2. Joyful jugglers: The China Acrobatic Troupe is staging a nightly variety show at the Tiandi Theatr...\n\nQ: On which page do the above passages most probably appear in the newspaper?", "options": ["Opinions.", "Business.", "Sports.", "Listings."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2095, "question": "A newspaper reporter's job can be very interesting.He meets all types of people and lives quite a busy life.He is _ for news all the time,then after several years he may get a desk job,and life becomes a bit more settled.Let's look at his work a little more closely.In a day he may have to interview the prime minister of a foreign country, and the next day he may be writing about a football match.Sometimes he may be so busy that he hardly has any time to sleep.And at other times he may go on for days looking out for news materials yet return empty--handed. In the beginning,a reporter has to cover a very wide field.After the early years he becomes more specialized in his work.For example,he may finaliy be asked to write only on court cases or politics or sports.Some reporters may become so s...\n\nQ: Reporters who write on films are said to be lucky because they  _  .", "options": ["can write anything they like", "can see more film stars", "can pay less than other people", "can see the fdms before most people see them in the cinema"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2736, "question": "We experience different forms of the Sun's energy every day. We can see its light and feel its warmth. The Sun is the major source of energy for our planet. It causes the evaporation of water from the oceans and lakes. Sunlight also provides the energy used by green plants to make their own food. These green plants then provide food for all organisms on the Earth. Much of the energy that comes from the Sun never reaches the Earth's surface. It is either reflected or absorbed by the gases in the upper atmosphere. Of the energy that reaches the lower atmosphere,30% is reflected by clouds or the Earth's surface. The remaining 70% warms the surface of the planet, causes water to evaporate, and provides energy for the water cycle and weather. Only a tiny part, approximately 0.023%, is actually ...\n\nQ: Only a small part of the Sun's energy reaches the Earth's surface because most of it is  _  .", "options": ["absorbed by the clouds in the lower atmosphere", "reflected by the gases in the upper atmosphere", "lost in the upper and lower atmosphere", "used to evaporate water from the oceans and lakes"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 916, "question": "Joe Temper should have known better. After all, he works for a large auto insurance company. It won't hurt to leave the key in the truck this once, he thought, as he filled his gas tank at a self-service gas station. But minutes later, as he was paying the money, he saw the truck being driven away. In 2010, 1.6 million motor vehicles were stolen in the United States --one every 20 seconds. If present trends continue, experts predict vehicle thefts could be over two million every year by the end of the decade. Vehicle theft is a common phenomenon, which has a direct effect on over four million people a year. The cost is astonishing. Many police officials blame professional thieves for the large number of the thefts. It is a major moneymaker for organized crime. Typically, stolen cars are ta...\n\nQ: What is NOT a reason for the increase of car theft as mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["Police don't give enough attention to car theft cases.", "More people parked their cars and left the keys inside.", "Measures and laws against car thieves are not effective enough.", "Car theft brings car thieves much money."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3269, "question": "If you have been joining in chat room conversations, or trading email with web pals , you have become one of the millions who write in a peculiarly short form of English. And you've got a sense of humor about short forms like SOHF (=\" sense\" of humor failure) to describe Internet newcomers who don't understand you. Across the globe, every night teenagers and their elders are \"talking online\", many of them all talking at the same time. It's fast: try talking to six people at once.It's brief: three or four words per exchange.It takes wit, concentration, and quick fingers. And it requires tremendous linguistic economy .There's neither time nor space for explanations.Why consume precious key-strokes telling six friends you have to leave for a moment to take care of your little brother when BRB...\n\nQ: Many people talk on the Internet    _   .", "options": ["by sending short emails", "by using a particular short form of English", "by using peculiar English words and expression", "in a funny way"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1523, "question": "Dear Ana, In your last letter, you told me that your boss Stephanie was probably looking for a new job and you didn't know how to tell her that you wanted to take her position if she left. Well, I'd like to tell you that there is no polite way to talk about this situation with your boss. After all, you are not one-hundred-percent sure that she is actually job-hunting. Even if you know for sure that she is, you can't, because it's not your business. Still, there are a couple of things that you can do to put yourself in a good position in case your boss does _ in the near future. First, you can have a general conversation with her about your career plans. Say something like, \"You've always been supportive of me, Stephanie, and I'd love you to give me some advice on my professional developmen...\n\nQ: According to Liz, if your boss is leaving for another job, you can  _  .", "options": ["ask your manager to give the position to you", "write to let him know you want his position", "let him know you want his position indirectly", "write a letter to your best friend for advice"], "answer": 2}]